missirosesviews.com 2018-11-20

# Media Kit / Privacy Policy

**PR Disclosure Policy**

_The FCC requires that bloggers disclose their review policy if reviews will be written._

My blog is extremely PR friendly!  I would love to **review**  your products, services, venues, etc for promotion on my blog and my other social media outlets listed below. I’m the mother of 4 awesome kids…2 girls (ages 22 and 24) and 2 rowdy boys (ages 8 and 12) in addition to my entourage of fur-babies, my adorable Chihuahua, and Cats. I LOVE to travel and stay at fun and interesting destinations as well…Pitch me!

**Social Media Outlets:**  
Missi Rose’s Views  

*Travel reviews and posts will also be shared on the [Travelocity Gnomad](http://www.travelocity.com/gnomads) site and all social media channels.

***Update: I was a contributor for the Examiner.com from January 2011 until July 2016, when the publication shut down operations. I also contributed to the CBS Local Examiner (Houston area.)**

**POLICIES**

One of the least expensive ways to promote your product/service is by being featured a blog, social media outlets or word of mouth.  If requested, I will review your product/service and an individual blog post will be dedicated to your review and organization. The post may contain photos and/or images. In order to review a product, a 

_full-size_

 sample should be provided to me so that I may give an accurate review after use. If for some reason I feel that a positive review should not be given, you will be contacted before the posting and given the choice of publication.

**Sponsored blog post** : I would love to write a blog post regarding your company or service. This may be in your words or mine, using any specified links, keywords or images. Fees are negotiable.

**Advertising opportunities**  in the form of banners, text and guest posts are available and rates are negotiable.  
**  
** **Disclosure**

This blog may accept forms of advertising, sponsorship and/or other forms of compensation. Any compensation received may influence the content, topics or posts of this blog. Any compensation will be identified as paid or sponsored. Any product claim, statistic or quote should always be verified with the company or party in question.

**Stats:**  
Google PR – 3  
MozRank – 4.25  
Facebook fans: 11700  
Twitter followers: 19200  
Pinterest followers: 4700  
Instagram followers: 2650  
Blog subscribers: 4400  
Examiner subscribers: 675 (see update above)

**Blog established: November 2011**

**Sponsor Recommendations:  **

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy policy sets out how uses and protects any information you give me when you use this website. Any information you via this blog will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. ** _Information I collect:_**

This blog may collect the following information:

1.    Your Name  
2.    Your Contact information, such as an email address

This information will be used for internal record keeping, and to allow to send you promotional emails about content on the site you might find interesting. This information will never be shared with a third party without your express consent, unless I am required to do so by law.

_**Cookies**_

This blog uses traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used most frequently, and this information is used in statistical analysis. This blog also uses cookies to help improve your experience of by remembering your preferences and tailoring content accordingly.

Most web browsers automatically accept ‘cookies’ but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies at any time, if you prefer. For more information please visit allaboutcookies.org

_**Further information**_

If you have previously agreed to using your personal information then you can change your mind at any time by emailing mel_rose6875@hotmail.com. You may also request a copy of any data held about you by under the Data Protection Act 1988. Such requests should be submitted to the email address above. A small charge may be made for providing this information.

If you believe any information holds on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email as soon as possible to the above address. Any inaccuracies will be corrected as soon as possible.

This privacy policy is effective from May 24, 2018.

**All questions, inquiries, and requests may be directed to Melissa Moreno at _mel_rose6875@hotmail.com_**
